Guide to the Francis J. McNamara papers, 1928-1997
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Anti-Communism and Subversive Activities, 1928-1975; (154 boxes)
  - China -"Exodus of Hungry Chinese People to Hong Kong", June 15, 1962 (Folder 8, Box 21)
    People's Republic of China
  - China - Far East Spotlight, 1948-1949 (Folder 9, Box 21)
  - China - Forging a New China - Lawrence K. Rosinger, 1948 (Folder 10, Box 21)
  - China - Free China and Asia, 1958-1962 (Folder 11, Box 21)
  - China - Free China and Asia, 1962-1963 (Folder 12, Box 21)
  - China - Free China and Asia, 1963-1964 (Folder 13, Box 21)
  - China - Free China and Asia, 1959 (Folder 1, Box 22)
  - China - Free China and Asia, 1960 (Folder 2, Box 22)
  - China - Free China and Asia, 1961 (Folder 3, Box 22)
  - China - Free China and Asia, 1965 (Folder 4, Box 22)
  - China - A Guidebook to 10 years of Secrecy in our China Policy, 1951 (Folder 5, Box 22)
  - China - Illustrated Books, ca. 1950s (Folder 6, Box 22)
  - China, key to the Orient and to Asia - Rev. William R. Johnson, 1950 (Folder 7, Box 22)
  - China - Mao Tse-Tung - Booklets, 1937-1958 (Folder 8, Box 22)
  - China Monthly Review, 1951 (Folder 9, Box 22)
  - China's Relief Needs, 1944 (Folder 10, Box 22)
  - China - The Shanghai News, 1950-1951 (Folder 11, Box 22)
  - China - Time magazine, April 1955 (Folder 12, Box 22)
  - China and the United Nations, 1960-1961 (Folder 13, Box 22)
    People's Republic of China, United Nations
  - China, 1950s (Folder 14, Box 22)
  - China, 1950s (Folder 1, Box 23)
  - China, 1950s (Folder 2, Box 23)
  - China, 1950-1992 (Folder 3, Box 23)
  - China, 1971-1983 (Folder 4, Box 23)
  - China (Communist) - "Facts" (Folder 5, Box 23)
  - China ([Joseph] Alsop, Lattimore, [Theodore H.] White, [Edgar] Snow, etc.), 1949-1995 (Folder 6, Box 23)
  - China ([Joseph] Alsop, Lattimore, [Theodore H.] White, [Edgar] Snow, etc.), 1949-1995 (Folder 7, Box 23)
  - China - "Communist Zoo", 1951 (Folder 8, Box 23)
  - China - Facts Forum Magazine., November 1956 (Folder 9, Box 23)
  - China - The American Legion Magazine., August, 1956 (Folder 10, Box 23)
  - China - The Reporter Magazine - "The China Lobby" including related papers., April 15, 1952 (Folder 11, Box 23)
  - China - The Reporter Magazine - "The China Lobby II", April 29, 1952 (Folder 12, Box 23)
  - China - The New Leader - "Formosa and Free World Policy", April 4, 1955 (Folder 13, Box 23)
  - China - "An Open Letter to International Friends", ca. 1950s (Folder 14, Box 23)
  - China - Letter from Joseph C. Grew - American-Asian Educational Exchange Inc., October 27, 1960 (Folder 1, Box 24)
  - China - American China Policy Association Inc. - letter to Sen. Fulbright., November 20, 1959 (Folder 2, Box 24)
  - China - Clergyman's Committee on China - information envelope, 1970 (Folder 3, Box 24)
  - China - "The Committee of One Million" Information., September 11, 1959 (Folder 4, Box 24)
  - China - "Plain Talk - Vol. III, No. 3 - Our Harvest in China" - by Alfred Kohlberg., December, 1948 (Folder 5, Box 24)
  - China - The Patrick Henry League Information and Letters, 1960 (Folder 6, Box 24)
  - China - "Georgia Seminar on American Strategy"., March 10-11, 1961 (Folder 7, Box 24)
  - China - "Some Facts Concerning the American Friends Service Committee", August 25, 1955 (Folder 8, Box 24)
  - China - "The New Leader - Communist China - fact and myth", ca. 1960s-1970s (Folder 9, Box 24)
  - China - "China and the Communist 'Peace Offensive' - Department of State", ca. 1950s (Folder 10, Box 24)
  - China - Fortune - "The Tyrannous Decade", February 1948 (Folder 11, Box 24)
  - China - "Between the Bear and the Dragon" by Christopher Rand "`, 1948 (Folder 12, Box 24)
  - China - Recognize Red China? From "Circuit Riders Inc.", 1958 (Folder 13, Box 24)
  - China - Time Magazine on China, ca. 1950s (Folder 14, Box 24)
  - China - Congressional Record: The China Lobby., 1952 (Folder 15, Box 24)
  - China Builds for the Future by George Kent., 1948 (Folder 16, Box 24)
  - China - Newspaper Clippings on China, 1948-1958 (Folder 17, Box 24)
  - Church Committee Staff, 1975-1977 (Folder 18, Box 24)
    CIA, Religion
  - Church Committee Staff, 1975-1977 (Folder 19, Box 24)
  - Churches and Communism, 1959-1960 (Folder 20, Box 24)
    Religion, Communism
  - Churchill, Winston, 1950-1953 (Folder 21, Box 24)
    USSR, Churchill
  - Churches, 1950-1994 (Folder 22, Box 24)
    Communist Party Membership, Clergy
  - CIA-Bella Abzug-FBI, 1970-1979 (Folder 23, Box 24)
    Central Intelligence Agency, Bella Abzug, Women's movements
  - CIA-Bella Abzug-FBI, 1970-1979 (Folder 24, Box 24)
  - CIA-[George H.W. Bush], 1975-1980 (Folder 25, Box 24)
    Central Intelligence Agency, Bush
  - CIA-cover, 1971-1981 (Folder 1, Box 25)
    Central Intelligence Agency
  - CIA-domestic acts, 1975-1977 (Folder 2, Box 25)
  - CIA-drugs, 1975-1977 (Folder 3, Box 25)
    Drugs, Central Intelligence Agency
  - CIA-drugs, 1975-1979 (Folder 4, Box 25)
  - CIA-education, religious, 1975-1981 (Folder 5, Box 25)
    Central Intelligence Agency, Religion
  - CIA-foreign source loss, 1975 (Folder 6, Box 25)
    Central Intelligence Agency, Espionage
  - CIA-House-[Lucien N.] Nedzi HSCI, 1975 (Folder 7, Box 25)
    House Committee on International Security, Central Intelligence Agency
  - CIA-House Panel [Mike] Pike, 1975-1980 (Folder 8, Box 25)
  - CIA-House Panel [Mike] Pike, 1975-1980 (Folder 9, Box 25)
  - CIA-media, 1973-1982 (Folder 10, Box 25)
    Central Intelligence Agency, Media
  - CIA-miscellaneous, 1969-1981 (Folder 11, Box 25)
    Espionage, Central Intelligence Agency
  - CIA-miscellaneous, 1969-1981 (Folder 12, Box 25)
  - CIA-Miscellaneous, 1959-1994 (Folder 1, Box 26)
  - CIA-morale, 1975-1982 (Folder 2, Box 26)
  - CIA-novels, films, etc., 1956-1985 (Folder 3, Box 26)
    Entertainment, Fiction, Central Intelligence Agency
  - CIA-novels, films, etc., 1956-1985 (Folder 4, Box 26)
  - CIA-personnel, 1974-1984 (Folder 5, Box 26)
  - CIA-police, 1973-1980 (Folder 6, Box 26)
    Central Intelligence Agency, Police
  - CIA- Washington Post expose, 1974-1975 (Folder 7, Box 26)
  - CIA-Reports [Soviet oil], 1975-1980 (Folder 8, Box 26)
    Coal, OPEC, Central Intelligence Agency
  - CIA-[law] suits and court decisions, 1974-1980 (Folder 9, Box 26)
  - Cities-miscellaneous-PD intelligence bans, 1973-1992 (Folder 10, Box 26)
  - Civil Defense, 1960-1986 (Folder 1, Box 27)
    Cold War, Bomb Shelters, Defense
  - Civil Defense, 1960-1987 (Folder 2, Box 27)
  - Clark, Ramsey, 1970-1977 (Folder 3, Box 27)
    Attorney General Ramsey Clark
  - CNSS, 1974-1981 (Folder 4, Box 27)
    Center for National Security Studies
  - CNSS, 1975-1978 (Folder 5, Box 27)
  - Code Security - NSA, 1971-1978 (Folder 6, Box 27)
    National Security Agency
  - Coffee houses - Jane Fonda, 1970-1971 (Folder 7, Box 27)
    Jane Fonda, U.S. Servicemen's Fund, Summer of Support, Support our Soldiers
  - C. O.'s, 1969-1971 (Folder 8, Box 27)
    Conscientious Objectors, Vietnam, Draft, Supreme Court
  - Colleges, 1950s (Folder 9, Box 27)
    Board of Higher Education, Investigation, Subversive Activities, Academic Freedom, McCarthyism
  - Colleges, 1950s (Folder 10, Box 27)
    Anti-War Protests, Student Protests, Anti-Communism, Academic Freedom, McCarthyism
  - Colleges, universities, 1952-1953 (Folder 11, Box 27)
    Subversive Activities, Anti-Communism, Academic Freedom, McCarthyism
  - Colleges, universities, 1952-1953 (Folder 1, Box 28)
    Anti-Communism, Senate Hearings, Academic Freedom, McCarthyism
  - Colleges, universities, 1951-1953 (Folder 2, Box 28)
  - Colleges, universities, 1951-1953 (Folder 3, Box 28)
  - Colleges, universities, 1953 (Folder 4, Box 28)
    Anti-Communism, Senate Hearings, Academic Freedom, McCarthyism, Communist Propaganda
  - Colleges, universities, 1953 (Folder 5, Box 28)
  - Colby, William E., 1974-1994 (Folder 6, Box 28)
  - Colby, William E. - Statements, 1975 (Folder 7, Box 28)
  - Colson, Charles W., 1974 (Folder 8, Box 28)
    Watergate, Nixon, Watergate Seven
  - Columbia Eagle Armed Forces Day, 1970 (Folder 9, Box 28)
    Anti-War Protests
  - Combatting communism, 1951-1953 (Folder 1, Box 29)
  - Commager [Henry Steels]-Thomas Paine-Providence, 1953-1956 (Folder 2, Box 29)
    Statue Controversy
  - Committee for Public Justice, 1970-1990 (Folder 3, Box 29)
    Justice Department, FBI
  - Committee of One Million, 1958 (Folder 4, Box 29)
    Anti-Communism, China, United Nations
  - Committee on Un-American Activities, 1956 (Folder 5, Box 29)
  - Committees Report Document, 1948 (Folder 6, Box 29)
    Committees in the U.S.
  - Common Cause, 1975-1980 (Folder 7, Box 29)
    Newspaper Clippings, Common Cause
  - Common Sense, 1956-1960 (Folder 8, Box 29)
    Anti-Communist Newspaper
  - Communication intercept telephone and cable, 1975-1978 (Folder 9, Box 29)
    Soviet Spying, Cold War, Intelligence
  - Communism, 1938-1958 (Folder 10, Box 29)
    History of Communism, Communist Party USA
  - Communism - Russian Writing, 1958 (Folder 11, Box 29)
    Anti-Communism, Russian language, Propaganda
  - Communism - general, 1947-1990 (Folder 1, Box 30)
  - Communists in Press and SISS Investigation, 1950s (Folder 2, Box 30)
    Communism, Media
  - Communist International, 1932 (Folder 3, Box 30)
  - Communists - Lists of people and organizations, 1950s (Folder 4, Box 30)
    Cold War, Communism
  - The Communist Manifesto - Blueprint for World Revolt, 1956 (Folder 5, Box 30)
    Cold War, Communism, Marx
  - Communist officers academies, 1970-1971 (Folder 6, Box 30)
  - Communist Origin and Manipulation of Vietnam Week, April 8-15, 1967 (Folder 7, Box 30)
    Communism, Vietnam
  - Communist Pamphlets and Publications, 1921-1953 (Folder 8, Box 30)
    Communism, Publications
  - Communist Pamphlets and Publications, 1921-1953 (Folder 9, Box 30)
  - Communist Perspective [folder 1 of 2], ca. 1950s (Folder 1, Box 31)
  - Communist Perspective [folder 2 of 2], ca. 1950s (Folder 2, Box 31)
  - The Communist Position on the Negro Question, 1947 (Folder 3, Box 31)
    Communism, Racism
  - Communist Power in U.S. Industry, 1947-1956 (Folder 4, Box 31)
    Communism, Industry
  - Communist teacher study, 1950-1990 (Folder 5, Box 31)
  - Communist teacher study, 1954 (Folder 6, Box 31)
  - Communist teacher study, 1965-1978 (Folder 7, Box 31)
  - Communist teacher study, 1965-1978 (Folder 8, Box 31)
  - Communists in the Trotsky Mold, 1971 (Folder 1, Box 32)
    Communism, Trotsky
  - Congress, 1950-1989 (Folder 2, Box 32)
    Anti-Communism, Congressional Records, McCarran-Walter Act
  - Congress, 1974-1976 (Folder 3, Box 32)
    Anti-Communism, Congressional Records, Senate Hearings
  - Congress, 1974-1976 (Folder 4, Box 32)
    Congressional Records, House Committees, Watergate, Opinion Polls
  - Congress-files, 1969-1980 (Folder 5, Box 32)
    FBI, HUAC
  - Congress-left, 1967-1978 (Folder 6, Box 32)
    Congressional Elections
  - Congress-ratings, 1971-1980 (Folder 7, Box 32)
    American Conservative Union
  - Constitution of the U.S.S.R., 1938 (Folder 8, Box 32)
    Constitution, USSR, National Council of American-Soviet Friendship
  - Copley News Service, 1969 (Folder 9, Box 32)
  - Copley News Service, 1969 (Folder 10, Box 32)
  - Copley News Service: Vietnam "moratorium" article and draft, 1969 (Folder 11, Box 32)
  - Copley Press, ca. 1969 (Folder 12, Box 32)
    Vietnam, Demonstrations, Protests
  - Conspiracy, 1972-1977 (Folder 1, Box 33)
    Legal Application
  - Coping - counter-terrorism - general, 1971-1984 (Folder 2, Box 33)
    Heritage Foundation, Domestic Intelligence, Terrorist Attacks
  - Correspondence - general, 1973-1988 (Folder 3, Box 33)
    Letters, William J. Casey, Abel E. Berland, Bob Woodward
  - [Correspondence: red channels], 1950-1952 (Folder 4, Box 33)
    Letters, Red Channels
  - Council Against Communist Aggression, 1956-1957 (Folder 5, Box 33)
    Council Against Communist Aggression, Correspondence, Documents, Records
  - Council Against Communist Aggression, 1951-1954 (Folder 6, Box 33)
  - Council Against Communist Aggression, 1962-1973 (Folder 7, Box 33)
  - Counterattack - Index, 1948-1954 (Folder 8, Box 33)
    Anti-Communism, Counterattack, Newsletter, Nonfiction
  - Counterattack - Vol. I, 1947 (Folder 9, Box 33)
  - Counterattack - Vol. II, 1948 (Folder 10, Box 33)
  - Counterattack - Vol. III, 1949 (Folder 1, Box 34)
  - Counterattack - Vol. IV, 1950 (Folder 2, Box 34)
  - Counterattack - Vol. V, 1951 (Folder 3, Box 34)
  - Counterattack - Vol. VI, 1952 (Folder 4, Box 34)
  - Counterattack - Vol. VII - Vol. VIII, 1953-1954 (Folder 5, Box 34)
  - Counterattack vol. 8, no. 20-vol. 9, no. 52, 1954-1955 (Folder 6, Box 34)
  - Counterattack vol. 10, no. 1-52, 1956 (Folder 1, Box 35)
  - Counterattack vol. 11, no. 1-52, 1957 (Folder 2, Box 35)
  - Counterattack vol. 12, no. 1-38, 1958 (Folder 3, Box 35)
  - Counterattack vol. 13, no. 1-26, 1959 (Folder 4, Box 35)
  - Counterattack vol. 14, no. 1-26, 1960 (Folder 5, Box 35)
  - Counterattack vol. 15, no. 1-26, 1961 (Folder 6, Box 35)
  - Counterattack vol. 16, no. 1-26, 1962 (Folder 1, Box 36)
  - Counterattack vol. 17, no. 1-26, 1963 (Folder 2, Box 36)
  - Counterattack vol. 18, no. 1-26, 1964 (Folder 3, Box 36)
  - Counterattack vol. 19, no. 1-13, 1965 (Folder 4, Box 36)
  - Counterattack - Correspondence, 1947-1959 (Folder 5, Box 36)
    Letters, Nonfiction, McNamara
  - Counterattack: legal, 1954-1956 (Folder 6, Box 36)
    American Business Consultants v. Joe Julian, Court Cases, New York State Court of Appeals
  - Counterattack: miscellaneous, ca. 1951 (Folder 7, Box 36)
    Kiwanis, Red Channels
  - Counterintelligence program, 1974-1981 (Folder 8, Box 36)
    Anti-Communism, Communist Party, Counterintelligence, Espionage
  - Court disruption (lawyers), 1970-1971 (Folder 9, Box 36)
    American College of Trial Lawyers, Disruption of Judicial Process
  - Courts-lawyers, 1950-1991 (Folder 10, Box 36)
    Courts, New York Bar
  - Courts-lawyers, 1970-1980 (Folder 1, Box 37)
    Court disruption, Lawyers
  - Courts-lawyers, 1970-1980 (Folder 2, Box 37)
    Investigation, Court Disruption, Lawyers
  - Courts-lawyers, 1958-1986 (Folder 3, Box 37)
    American Bar Association, Movement Lawyers
  - Courts-lawyers, 1958-1986 (Folder 4, Box 37)
    Supreme Court, Warren E. Berger
  - CPUSA, 1969-1994 (Folder 5, Box 37)
    Communist Party USA, Information Digest, Newspaper Clippings
  - CPUSA, 1969-1994 (Folder 6, Box 37)
    Communist Party USA, Newspaper Clippings
  - CPUSA, 1956-1992 (Folder 7, Box 37)
    Communist Party USA, Newspaper Clippings, Letters, Congressional Records
  - CPUSA, 1955-1994 (Folder 8, Box 37)
    Communist Party USA, Newspaper Clippings, Letters
  - CPUSA, 1955-1994 (Folder 9, Box 37)
    Communist Party USA, Correspondence, Political Affairs
  - CPUSA, 1954-1981 (Folder 1, Box 38)
    Communist Party USA, Editorials, Newspaper Clippings
  - CPUSA, 1949-1990 (Folder 2, Box 38)
  - Crime-courts-evidence-weapons, 1970-1985 (Folder 3, Box 38)
    Supreme Court, Newspaper Clippings
  - Crime-violence-general, 1975-1976 (Folder 4, Box 38)
    Newspaper Clippings
  - Crouch, Paul, 1954 (Folder 5, Box 38)
    Crouch, Paul
  - Cuba, 1973-1980 (Folder 6, Box 38)
  - Curtis-Emerson-McNamara, 1965 (Folder 7, Box 38)
    Congressional Record
  - DOD version (Pentagon papers), 1971 (Folder 8, Box 38)
    Department of Defense, Pentagon papers
  - Dallin, David J., ca. 1939-1942 (Folder 9, Box 38)
    Facts on Communism, Soviet Union, Secret Police (Checka)
  - Damage issue, 1971-1973 (Folder 10, Box 38)
    Pentagon Papers, Newspaper Clippings
  - Davis, Angela, 1969-1980 (Folder 11, Box 38)
    Black Movements, Militant, Subversive Activity, Newspaper Clippings
  - Davis, Angela, 1970-1971 (Folder 12, Box 38)
  - Davis, Angela - Dellinger, David, 1970-1993 (Folder 13, Box 38)
  - Davis, Rennie, 1969-1977 (Folder 14, Box 38)
    Antiwar, Activists, Protests
  - D. C. [District of Colombia], 1973-1983 (Folder 1, Box 39)
    District of Colombia, Newspaper Clippings
  - D. C. [District of Colombia], 1973-1983 (Folder 2, Box 39)
  - D. C. [District of Colombia], 1973-1983 (Folder 3, Box 39)
  - D. C. [District of Colombia], 1973-1983 (Folder 4, Box 39)
  - DC court decisions re., 1975-1982 (Folder 5, Box 39)
    District of Colombia, Courts, Newspaper Clippings
  - Defections, 1971-1987 (Folder 6, Box 39)
  - Dellums [Ronald V. and] Dell, 1969-1976 (Folder 7, Box 39)
    Conscientious Objectors, Draft, Vietnam
  - Dellums [Ronald V. and] Dell, 1970-1993 (Folder 8, Box 39)
  - Dellums [Ronald V. and] Dell, 1970-1984 (Folder 9, Box 39)
  - Dellums [Ronald V.] and [Mike] Gravel, 1972 (Folder 1, Box 40)
  - Dellums [Ronald V.] and HASC, 1973-1991 (Folder 2, Box 40)
    Congress, Dellums, Ronald, B-2 Bomber
  - Dellums [Ronald V.] - Pike and ethics committees, 1975-1976 (Folder 3, Box 40)
    Congress, Dellums, Ronald, Ethics Committee, Pike Committee
  - Dellums [Ronald V.] and Nedy, 1975 (Folder 4, Box 40)
    Congressional Records, Dellums, Ronald
  - Dellums [Ronald V.] and VALB, 1959-1985 (Folder 5, Box 40)
    Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade, Spanish Civil War
  - Democratic Convention, 1972 (Folder 6, Box 40)
    Convention, Democratic Party, Newspaper Clippings
  - Democratic House revolt ('reform'), 1975 (Folder 7, Box 40)
    Congress, House of Representatives, New Senators, Reform
  - Dennis, Eugene, 1947-1948 (Folder 8, Box 40)
    Anti-Communism, Dennis, Eugene, Nonfiction, Pamphlets,
  - Dent - White House - Vietnam - Nixon, 1968-1973 (Folder 9, Box 40)
    Nixon, Richard, Vietnam
  - Department of the Army: Civil Disturbance Information Collection Plan, 1968 (Folder 10, Box 40)
    Department of the Army, Confidential, War Office
  - Department of Justice, 1961-1972 (Folder 11, Box 40)
    Anti-Communist Cases, Department of Justice, Reports, Subversive Activities Control Board
  - Deportations, 1950-1952 (Folder 12, Box 40)
    Deportations, Newspaper Clippings
  - Deserters, 1966-1971 (Folder 13, Box 40)
    Sweden, American Deserters
  - Design for Survival, 1968 (Folder 14, Box 40)
    American Security Council, Comic, General Thomas S. Power, National Security
  - DGI-Cuba, 1960-1987 (Folder 15, Box 40)
    Cuban Intelligence Network, KGB
  - DIA [Defense Intelligence Agency], 1969-1987 (Folder 16, Box 40)
    Congressional Reports, Newspaper Clippings
  - The Diary of General Grow, 1952 (Folder 17, Box 40)
    Diary, Expose, Kahn, Albert E.
  - Disinformation, 1966-1988 (Folder 1, Box 41)
    Congressional Record, The Heritage Foundation, Newspaper Clippings
  - Displaced persons, 1950 (Folder 2, Box 41)
    Communism, Newspaper Clippings, Switzerland
  - D. J. (Department of Justice), 1953-1984 (Folder 3, Box 41)
    Agee, Classified Information, Department of Justice
  - D. J. (Department of Justice), 1954-1989 (Folder 4, Box 41)
    Attorney General, Communist Cases, Department of Justice
  - DOD directives CP line, 1969 (Folder 5, Box 41)
    Communist Party, Department of Defense
  - Domestic Intelligence, 1973-1994 (Folder 6, Box 41)
    Intelligence, National Security, Newspaper Clippings
  - Donohoe vs. Duling, 1972 (Folder 7, Box 41)
    Laird vs. Tatum
  - Donner, Frank, 1953-1980 (Folder 8, Box 41)
    ACLU, Anti-Communism, Surveillance
  - Draft attacks, convicts, 1969-1970 (Folder 9, Box 41)
    Defense, Draft Dogers, Riots, Vietnam
  - Draft California [and] Puerto Rico, 1969-1970 (Folder 10, Box 41)
    Draft Protests, Puerto Rico, Vietnam
  - Draft-counselling, 1968-1971 (Folder 11, Box 41)
    Vietnam Draft, Lawyers
  - Draft-court decisions, 1969-1970 (Folder 1, Box 42)
    Courts, Draft Avoidance, Deferments, Trials
  - Draft orgd'd resistance Democrats, 1969-1971 (Folder 2, Box 42)
    Draft, Vietnam Protests
  - Draft-tech-general, 1965-1970 (Folder 3, Box 42)
    Selective Service, News
  - Draft-tech-general, 1965-1970 (Folder 4, Box 42)
  - Dulles, John Foster, 1950-1953 (Folder 5, Box 42)
    China, Far East, United States Foreign Policy
  - Earth Day, 1971 (Folder 6, Box 42)
    FBI, Earth Day Rallies, Spies
  - Eisenhower, 1950s (Folder 7, Box 42)
    Newspaper Clippings, Press Conference Transcript
  - Eisenhower, Dwight, 1951-1953 (Folder 8, Box 42)
    Inaugural Address, State of the Union, Speeches
  - Elections, 1950-1953 (Folder 9, Box 42)
    Congressional Elections, Election Results
  - Elections, 1954 (Folder 10, Box 42)
    Election Results
  - Ellsberg [Daniel] tap, 1971-1978 (Folder 1, Box 43)
    FBI, Pentagon Papers
  - Ellsberg [Daniel] trial and background, 1971-1981 (Folder 2, Box 43)
    Ellsberg, Daniel, Pentagon, Press Leak, Vietnam
  - Ellsberg [Daniel] trial and background, 1971-1981 (Folder 3, Box 43)
  - Eldridge Cleaver, 1968-1994 (Folder 4, Box 43)
    Cleaver, Eldridge, Newspaper Clippings
  - Emergency Detention Act of 1950 Amendments, 1970-1971 (Folder 5, Box 43)
    Congress, House of Representatives
  - Emerson, Thomas I., 1950-1991 (Folder 6, Box 43)
    Individual Freedom, Emerson, Thomas, Smith Act
  - Ervin, Sam J. and committee, 1953-1981 (Folder 7, Box 43)
    Anti-Communism, Arrests, Congressional Record, Counterattack
  - Espionage, 1960-1985 (Folder 8, Box 43)
    Anti-Communism, Arrests, KGB, Soviet Spy Network, Trials
  - Espionage, 1960-1985 (Folder 9, Box 43)
    Arrests, KGB, Soviet Spy Network
  - Espionage, 1960-1985 (Folder 10, Box 43)
  - Espionage, 1956-1979 (Folder 11, Box 43)
    Arrests, KGB, NATO, Soviet Spy Network
  - Espionage, 1956-1979 (Folder 1, Box 44)
    Arrests, KGB, Soviet Spy Network, Soviet Secret Police
  - Espionage, 1956-1979 (Folder 2, Box 44)
    Arrests, KGB, Soviet Spy Network, Yugoslavia
  - Espionage Statute, 1971-1986 (Folder 3, Box 44)
    Senate Subcommittee, Soviet Spies
  - Ex-communists, 1951-1954 (Folder 4, Box 44)
    Anti-Communism, Communist Party Recruiters, Trial Witnesses
  - Executive order 10450 amendment, 1967-1970 (Folder 5, Box 44)
    Security Requirements for Government Employment
  - Executive Order 10450 security clearances, 1957-1988 (Folder 6, Box 44)
  - Executive Order 10450 security clearances, 1957-1988 (Folder 7, Box 44)
  - Executive Order 10450 security clearances, 1957-1989 (Folder 8, Box 44)
  - Executive Order 10450 security clearances, 1957-1990 (Folder 9, Box 44)
  - Executive order 11605, 1953-1971 (Folder 10, Box 44)
    Nixon, Security Requirements for Government Employment, Subversive Activities Control Board
  - Executive order 11605, 1953-1971 (Folder 1, Box 45)
  - Executive Order 11605-Ervin sub-committee hearings, 1971 (Folder 2, Box 45)
  - Executive Order 11605-Ervin sub-committee hearings, 1971 (Folder 3, Box 45)
  - Executive Order 11605 - lawsuit, 1971-1972 (Folder 4, Box 45)
  - Executive Order 11605 - lawsuit, 1971-1972 (Folder 5, Box 45)
  - Exhibits no. 1 through no. 46, 1971 (Folder 6, Box 45)
    Daily World, Subversive Activities Control Board
  - Exhibits no. 1 through no. 46, 1971 (Folder 7, Box 45)
    Subversive Activities Control Board
  - Exhibits no. 1 through no. 46, 1971 (Folder 1, Box 46)
  - Facts and documents concerning the Far East, 1948 (Folder 2, Box 46)
    National Conference on American Policy in China and the Far East
  - Family and political conflict, 1951-1952 (Folder 3, Box 46)
    Anti-Communism, Kidnapping, Newspaper Clippings
  - Family Jewels, 1967-1969 (Folder 4, Box 46)
    Illegal or Inappropriate CIA Activity 1950s to 1970s
  - Farmers, 1950s (Folder 5, Box 46)
    Agriculture, Anti-Communism, Communist Infiltration
  - Farrakhan, Louis, 1961-1995 (Folder 6, Box 46)
    Nation of Islam, Newspaper Clippings
  - FBI, 1950-1978 (Folder 7, Box 46)
    Arrests, Communist Plots, Newspaper Clippings
  - FBI, 1950-1978 (Folder 8, Box 46)
  - FBI-Arlington apartment bust-in, 1975-1978 (Folder 9, Box 46)